Guide to the United Scenic Artists Records WAG.065
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: General Files, 1897-1984
  - Painter's Fees, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Pension Fund, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Petitions, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Picket List, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Plautus Productions, Aug 1965-Oct 1966 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - President's Report (Covering 1923-1924), Jul 1925 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Protective Alliance of Scenic Painters of America: Reunion (card), Jan 27, 1897 (Box 7, Folder 25a)
  - Resolutions, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Romano, Arthur: Financial Correspondence (Largely Local 350, Chicago), 1940, 1947-1968 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - S. Wolf's Sons: Centenary Article, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Sacher and Sacher, Counselors at Law: Correspondence, 1943-1951 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Scene Painting: Opera News Magazine, Feb 1969 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Scenic Design: General, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Screen Directors International Guild, Oct 1961-Dec 1961 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Sign-Pictoral and Display Union, Local 230, Feb 1955-Jun 1956 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Signal Corps Photographic Center, 1943, 1947-1956 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Steward Complaints by Studios, May 1947-Aug 1952 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Stock Bonding, Dec 1941-Mar 1942 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Strike, Jun 1947-Dec 1949 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Stylists for Motion Pictures: Directory, 1960-1969 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Summer Stock: List of Companies, 1940-1942 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Television: Correspondence, May 1947-Dec 1948 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Television: Correspondence, Jan 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Television: Correspondence, Jun 1950-Sep 1951 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Television: WPIX, 1951-1957 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Theatre of the Living Arts, 1934-1965 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Theatrical Costume Workers Union No. 21313: Correspondence, 1940-1944 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Trainee Program Agreement, 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Unemployment Committee, 1932-1935 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Withdrawal Card, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Volz, August, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Wardle, Fred v. Herbert Gahagan, Nov 1952-Dec 1952 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Ways and Means Committee Reports, 1933-1935 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Welfare Fund, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - World War II Productions: American Theatre Wing, etc., 1942-1946 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - World's Fair: United Scenic Artists Brochure, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Artwork, graphics, 1938, undated (Box 7, Folder 55-59)
- Series IV: Oversized Material, 1930-1972
  - Angelo, Waldo v. Florence Klotz et al. (re: Harold Prince's "Follies"), New York State Supreme Court Case, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Diorama and Display Workers: Agreements, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook: Clippings, Photographs, Playbills and Reviews (bound volume), 1930-1949 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Von Wicht, John, Society of Designer-Craftsmen, portfolio (Box 2)